The ambulance is coming.
Hello, Mom.
Yes, just arrived.
Don't worry about me being right.
Yes.
This.
In summary, will you stand staring at me for a long time?
Come on in.
Ah, sit here.
Ah, drink the water first.
Oh, is this Bug's house? It's so beautiful. Is Bug's alone?
Did you just remember me? My grandson, my aunt, when I was young, I liked to play at your house often.
Is this finished talking or finished talking? Follow me. I'll take you to see the room.
This is your bedroom.
Wow, the room is so beautiful.
But this house has its rules.
Rule number one, if going home beyond 8 p.m., must call or tell LINE.
Rule number two, pick up the ram from where to put it there.
The third rule part.
This is the most important. Do not mess with my desk.
This is my number.
If there's nothing important, don't call.
Like this
Is this elder or father?
Aunt T.
Yes, elder
Why are you dressed like this?
Yes.
Looking for drinking water, I'll be in the room for a while.
So let me set the fourth rule. You have to get dressed before you leave the room, okay?
Yes, elder
Hello
I'm not here.
Yeah, meet at the classroom. I'll hurry to go.
Uh, okay, okay.
Hey, why don't you look at the eyes of the boat?
The more people hurry
Younger
Why are you saying this?
You walked into you.
You have to apologize to me.
Why are you saying this?
What will you do?
The coffee is all six.
Look at you.
Do you have eyes?
The coffee is spilled. My shirt is all gone.
How will you be responsible?
Oh, yeah.
Will you take this?
Yeah.
Finish
Children today have no manners.
Hello, A. Bully.
Yeah, that's it.
Hello there.
Velkam to class
Welcome everyone to the X Y Sad Zero Zero One.
It's a subject to study about enhancing everyone's imagination.
Studying with today, the teacher named Nieti is moral.
Before coming to start the class, everyone knows the name of the teacher. We will come to know the name of friends, friends first.
What is your name
My name is
Who is she?
I
Ok, Beljan. Very excellent. The next person. Let's get to know the next friend. What is your name? Jujube. Jujube. Where are you from? Nakhon Pathom. Oh, Nakhon Pathom. Teacher likes to eat this. Pormalo. Pormalo. What are you doing?
It's a great student. Fresh. On the first day, it's late.
welcome
come in
What's your name? Why is she so handsome?
This subject, they don't talk.
We bought some snacks.
Thank you
she she she she
Eat a lot so you can grow quickly.
Um, but what's your name again?
Odd, my name is Nt.
Minute, June, minute. Ouch. Come in.
I tune. The E-play on my side is Earth.
Hi, Earth.
Hi, minutes.
Hi.
Where did you come from? Where did you stay? Where did you have a girlfriend?
Oh, I graduated from a provincial school and now I'm staying with a real elder. Actually, not really. He's the child of a mother's friend and now doesn't have a girlfriend.
Jae Dee is our girlfriend?
E. June E. Termites
His face is like a goddess.
Why would he come to the catfish hit the dam like you?
Some sailors
Hey, really ask.
Are you okay with me?
I've seen you so frustrated since morning.
Hey, you want a cane?
In the morning, I met a psychopath, a crook. No, I don't know. He came to bump into me. He's all my own stream. He also called me a thousand money. So I gave it to the end.
Do you think this will end easily?
I won't let it. I hit me and say like I'm the wrong person. The worst. Give me a thousand money and say that this story will end. I don't need money. I need an apology. Sorry, sincere. You understand?
What are you going to do? Do you know what your name is?
Ugh, I don't know.
Hello, sir.
This is my friend.
My name is Sun. I'm still single.
Did you just eat?
My story doesn't have to be messy.
Then I'll do my homework first.
Bastard
Who is that?
Why is he so cute?
And does he have a girlfriend?
You know?
I don't know.
If you want to know
You went to ask him yourself.
Then can I flirt?
Hey, I'm just joking. Why do you have to stuff up?
Oh, elder Phuton, taste my boiled rice?
I intend to do it a lot.
No, I don't like boiled rice.
Elder brother
I intend to do a lot.
Are you really not going to taste my boiled rice?
No.
Then I go to study first
I saw it and it was a pity.
In truth, it's not delicious.
I told you, I don't like boiled rice.
And another thing
I'm afraid people around here are sorry.
I can't see what that is.
Also, I just
Forget the phone.
Eat well.
Don't eat
Not delicious.
This.
This is the spotted black.
What's wrong today?
Can't lose this often
I have a sub exam.
If I don't catch the exam
I'll have your mother turn you out now.
I'm not taking you anymore.
Oh, what's wrong with the car? Can you send it?
You.
Who's your brother?
My name is
Please call my name.
I never told you my name.
Will you know?
Listen and remember.
My name is Earth.
The next day will be called
And my name is Oppa.
What's wrong with the car?
Do you want to send me?
I'm not a mechanic.
If you know, I'll fix it myself.
No, you just ask well. Answer like you don't know. Will you send it?
Don't be busy. It's not about you.
Then please follow your heart. Go to the exam in time. I don't know.
Elder
That's you.
I can let you go.
See it as a pass.
But don't be afraid.
I'll pay for your time.
Value
Ah
What value?
Waste of time
Take it
So we don't have anything else.
Can't I get it?
Considering you owe me a favor.
Right?
Oh, hey.
Oh my brother
Huh? Who was that?
I see
Your child?
Cute
Where are you cute?
The face is like a catfish.
Habits are fucking bad
This person
That the other day made me study late
And still calling me a thousand
You
Yeah?
At first I thought that your friend
And you said you don't like him
Then why did he send it?
Ow you
It's a long story.
Now hurry to study first
I won't be able to take the sub exam again.
There must be something.
Hey, you tell me first, or you'll keep it to eat alone.
Don't be delirious. I told you. I don't like active men like it. I really hate it.
Ancient times say to hate, however often.
No way.
Hundred billion percent
And I will wait and see
Ah, sweep here too. Clean that pile. Get it done. Very important there.
Ratna, don't make up when friends work.
Found a little more here, take it clean
Ah, you guys.
When it's a club, hmm. Come in quickly. No lack, no donkey, not late enough. It's a teacher class.
Oh, teacher, isn't it the same? Classrooms are boring to die. Club rooms are much more fun.
And what are you doing? Don't tell me that you ordered me again.
The teacher is the mentor of our club. How can the teacher not come?
Then why don't I know alone?
Well, you're stupid. What did June ever know?
It's okay. My girlfriend knows about it alone. That's enough. My girlfriend is the cutest.
Oh, accidentally, just a moment, the powder is always hot.
Oh, nat. Baby, baby, stop.
Master, the papers you ordered.
Is that right?
ah wait
a moment
And the seniors like you have a concept yet, whether to go to Hua Hin or Pattaya Conrad for the teacher as well, because the teacher has to watch sports and is very important. Seniors like you, don't forget to check Budget well, is that enough?
Children, children, teachers must go first. Master has a meeting. Take good care of each other. Bye.
You think going to the camp at sea this time will definitely be fun.
Actually, I said that I will prepare a swimsuit. Um, seven, eight sets.
Are you crazy?
Go to camp for only three days
Will you wear three sets a day?
Why don't you? Ugh!
I'm sorry.
June, right?
Yes.
Today, would you like to invite June to eat and grill together?
Ah, can June give you an answer in the evening?
Yeah, yeah. Ah.
Ah.
Then I'll have your number.
Yes, sir.
Here. Thank you.
You are my friend. I don't dare to go alone. Go together.
Well, can we not go? We haven't called to tell elder Tak yet and we can't drink too.
It's about drinking. There's no one since birth. This kind of thing has to learn. As for the call, ask for elder Tak. Bring the number. We'll call.
I think it's good to be a friend. Hey, for a long time, when a man flirts, it's considered to make merit for him.
Let's go together. As for the clothes, don't worry. On the car, there are a lot.
Um, well, fine.
Yeah.
No one is considered to have called. I assume that Phra Thuang has allowed me to travel with you.
Today, I'm sorry. I got a lot of traffic.
It's okay, my friend is right.
But today you made an appointment. What business do you have?
Well, like this, today, I want this picture very much.
He wants you to draw this picture. As for the money, he can't pay.
And when will his client take it?
Can it be a few weeks?
A few weeks.
Oh, not in time. We are afraid not finished in time. Another thing is afraid that the quality of the work is not good.
Please accept
Please.
Don't tell me you
I already accepted him.
You are everywhere.
June is full today, Nanny.
June, did you call me to invite me to be your friend?
Oh, I told you. I said that fully.
You don't have to think too much. Eat and eat again.
I'll be here.
Hello?
What?
Oh elder
June, my friend cares.
Oh, now it's San after Mo.
Oh, that's it.
Oh.
Elder, I'm going home first.
I think you starve again.
Again?
Yeah.
You.
My brother
I took you home.
Oh, good luck.
So cute
Perth, why don't you want to talk to me? Why do you always have to be tense at me? I asked you to answer.
Drunk and quiet
Wait a minute.
June, right?
Yeah.
Uh, uh...
Is
Uh, uh,
Uh, would that be nice?
Yes
What is this?
June number
Oh no, I want my number.
Yes.
What is it? I don't know.
Uh, excuse me, sir.
Today, traffic jam
Yes.
Don't drink drunk again tonight.
I don't want to wipe you.
Do you think there's something strange?
How weird?
Follow me
Elder friend
Elder friend, he saw all of our little elephants.
Not really.
What are you smiling at?
I saw you smiling alone for a long time.
That's it.
No, who's smiling?
Um, that's it. But you came to send me this morning, elder Tak, right? Why is he so handsome?
How did you guys see each other?
It's the two of us.
No, nothing, nothing.
No, I don't want to have a girlfriend. I want to study hard first.
Yes, but if I have a girlfriend, I have to be a mistress. Other people must be mistresses. Okay?
Enough. Do you ask first if he wants you?
What are you going to do with me?
You are the devil until I was early.
That's enough. I think it's better to go to school first.
Not stuck yet
Q Master hopes that everyone will understand. And then Fairy Importen. The work that the teacher ordered. Don't forget. Send to On Time.
Because this work affects all of you.
What? Order work and don't tell.
Master, what work does the teacher order?
No, no sending, just addicted to F, because the teacher told them to give them to pay, add, pay, but the mobile phone gives the mobile phone, it tells you what the job is.
You, you two too. Eat snacks. Give your snacks. It tells you what the work is. Ratna, you too. Give me a powder puff. You tell me. Don't forget. I can't do it. I'm addicted to F.
Oh, Master.
Don't be mean to us.
Tell us
Ok student
Ennofti class. Bye.
Notice that the two sides are equal, right? When the two sides are equal, put the straight values in the problem and you have something to ask?
You guys are like this. If we teach, you guys are like this. Next, we won't teach you anymore.
Who is going to have a heart and heart to listen to you?
Yes, we should be addicted to F.
When the teacher teaches, they don't listen to each other. Really?
Got it. His girlfriend, June, promised to study hard, not stubborn, not naughty anymore.
Me too. Elder, I promise that I will study hard, not stubborn like this termite anymore.
Yeah, what kind of work did the teacher order?
Well, Master Niti ordered us to skate the picture into the A-four, right?
Wow, what's the job?
Sun
Saw sitting in front of stress for a long time
There is something to say.
Is
Well, you don't have to stress about the painting, because anyway, it's done in time.
It's not about that.
It's not that. What are you about?
I really asked you.
Are you and Nati really brothers?
Um, yeah.
Do you remember that day?
That day I said I liked it.
Um, I really like his brother. I came to tell you this day because I saw that you are my best friend and the ruler of Nani too, so I came to notice but didn't ask for permission.
Whatever you want, if you flirt with him, you hurry to flirt because me and his brother are fine. And on the other hand, I will make a decision for him. It would be impossible.
Must be like this, dear friend
Elder
Thank you
Probably don't have to eat it anymore. This forest probably has to eat with Sun.